Okay, 2Quad,
what we're going to do here is you're going to go into the
Client, TopicBatch,
Schedule, TopicBatch,
and Launch. Farm,
Schedule, you're going to go into this Conversation,
and then you're going to type in,
Claude, can you give me the
update? Topic and Content
Batch. by now, there are already new
topics. Or,
next. to be submitted next week,
to be submitted next week,
in the long form,
and content batch, batch as well.
or next organize them,
like, last time.
So, you don't have to take this by,
by verbatim. What I need you to do,
is to. Write something like this,
then, prompt, clod.
Okay, so, let us assume that this is already done
loading. So,
let's take Mason for an example.
He is in progress. He is due by October
13, which is next Monday. What you're going to do is open
this,
then open this,
the topic sheet, and then open this, the column. Now,
what you're going to do is download the meeting transcript.
It is imperative to download the meeting transcript
in empty file. Very,
very important. Once downloaded,
open up the Plot tab,
and then what you're going
to do is go to Maze one.
Here,
Maze on L. Upload the MD
file, download the topic sheet and PDF.
Upload it here, and then what you're going to do is
prompt it like this.
Something like this. Please,
in verbatim, please prompt it like this.
Now,
after you prompt it, it will,
it will show you something like this.
topic number one. Topic,
Vehicle, Status. As you can see,
it is connected. Topic two is given.
Topic three is kept,
kept, kept. Six and seven is not discussed. This is because I think it
is a topic B. A no answer even,
I believe. No answer needed.
Oh yeah. Okay,
so in this, topic six is type A,
which means we are not going to include this.
Topic B. No answer needed,
which is included.